downloads.ws 2016-03-14

# Privacy Policy

We respect your privacy and we are committed to safeguarding your privacy while online at our site downloads.ws . The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site.

**Log Files** :  
Like most standard Web site servers we use log files. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track users movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information.

**Advertisers** :  
We use outside ad companies to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies and are collected by our ad companies, and we do not have access to this information. We work with the ad companies:  
[TribalFusion.com](http://www.tribalfusion.com/) , [Google Adsense](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/ads/), [BuySellAds.com](http://www.buysellads.com/) . Please check their websites for respective privacy policies.

**Cookies & 3rd Party Advertisements**:  
Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>.

 **Contact** :

If users have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at: admin@downloads.ws
